<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<indexing>
 <paragraph index="9" node_type="writer">Email 1: Requesting an Assignment Extension</paragraph>
 <paragraph index="10" node_type="writer">Subject: Extension Request: Digital Literacy Project – Astitva Anand Srivastava - 25BMR10002</paragraph>
 <paragraph index="11" node_type="writer">Dear Professor, </paragraph>
 <paragraph index="12" node_type="writer">I am writing to respectfully request a 48-hour extension on the Digital Literacy Project assignment, originally due on March 31st.</paragraph>
 <paragraph index="13" node_type="writer">Unfortunately, I have experienced an unexpected technical failure with my primary laptop, which has temporarily hindered my ability to finalize the GitHub repository uploads. I am currently using the university computing lab to restore my files and aim to submit the completed work by April 2nd. </paragraph>
 <paragraph index="14" node_type="writer">Thank you for your time and for considering my request. </paragraph>
 <paragraph index="15" node_type="writer">Sincerely, </paragraph>
 <paragraph index="16" node_type="writer">Astitva Anand Srivastava</paragraph>
 <paragraph index="17" node_type="writer">Reg No: 25BMR10002</paragraph>
 <paragraph index="18" node_type="writer">B.Tech CSE Core (2025-2029)</paragraph>
 <paragraph index="19" node_type="writer">VIT Bhopal University</paragraph>
 <paragraph index="21" node_type="writer">Email 2: Internship Inquiry</paragraph>
 <paragraph index="22" node_type="writer">Subject: Summer Internship Inquiry - Chaitanya Vaidya - B.Tech CSE Core </paragraph>
 <paragraph index="23" node_type="writer">Dear Internship Coordinator, </paragraph>
 <paragraph index="24" node_type="writer">I am a first-year B.Tech Computer Science student at VIT Bhopal University. I am writing to express my strong interest in potential summer internship opportunities at your organization within the software development department.</paragraph>
 <paragraph index="25" node_type="writer">Through my coursework and independent projects, I have developed a foundational understanding of digital collaboration and version control using GitHub. I am eager to apply my technical skills in a professional environment and contribute to your team’s objectives.</paragraph>
 <paragraph index="26" node_type="writer">My digital portfolio, which showcases my recent projects and certifications, can be viewed here: https://github.com/chaitanyaofficialhq-blip.</paragraph>
 <paragraph index="27" node_type="writer">Thank you for your time and consideration. I look forward to the possibility of discussing how I might contribute to your company. </paragraph>
 <paragraph index="28" node_type="writer">Best regards, </paragraph>
 <paragraph index="29" node_type="writer">Astitva Anand Srivastava</paragraph>
 <paragraph index="30" node_type="writer">Reg No: 25BMR10002</paragraph>
 <paragraph index="31" node_type="writer">B.Tech CSE Core (2025-2029)</paragraph>
 <paragraph index="32" node_type="writer">VIT Bhopal University</paragraph>
</indexing>
